Thank you for watching.
Good morning, everyone.
It's very windy here.
So today...
We're here to make a bonfire.
It's very sunny and clear.
And this time...
I have more camping gear for bonfires.
Or rather, I had bought some.
I'd like to open them and introduce them to you all.
I bought a lot of things, so I'd like to do more and more!
Here it is!
Ta-da!
What is this?
Please comment your guesses now!
We're going to open it now!
Please write all your predictions in the comments.
This is very important!
I think it's indispensable to build a fire.
All right.
If we do it this way...
I repeat.
Okay, see you later.
Opening before Dad 시 UHWU Eru
It's done!
It's a desk!
Up until now, I've actually been
I've been working on it
but I bought a cool desk!
I bought a cool desk!
Smells great!
It's so good!
And, and, and, and, and...
Optional.
Hmm? This? Oh, this one.
I got that as an option.
I'll show you what it is.
I'd like to show you...
I'm going to show you right now.
I'm going to show you what it is.
Here we go.
This way.
I wonder...
What's this?
Ta-da!
At first glance, it's just a...
A black board
But...
Ladies and gentlemen...
Look at this.
This one...
The beautiful board...
Next time, we will show you mom's favorite snacks!
Enjoy the next installment!
There are three boards attached, and you can remove them to make a black iron plate.
You can put something hot on it.
If you use your hands, you can't put much on it.
but with this one, you can put hot things on it as it is.
How convenient!
That's why I bought this table.
It's so cute!
Next, these two are the last of the big ones we have now.
Then I would like to introduce the smaller ones.
Then, I'll show you the smaller ones, since there are so many of them!
First of all, here they are!
Ta-da!
It's gloved, like a glove!
What do you call this?
What do you really call them?
Well, I guess it's a glove, isn't it?
I bought them because I have been feeling very hot with my bare hands.
It's cute.
So cute!
It's not too hot.
I put them on without feeling hot, hot, hot.I'm putting it down without it being hot, hot, hot.
This one looks like a river.
This one, you can hold something hot.
Okay, then.
Hey, guys.
Hey.
What's going on?
Something's not right.
Yes, sir.
Right?
Hey.
You know...
Yes.
Two weeks ago, that
Video
Do you remember it?
Two weeks ago.
That video
self-introduction video
Do you remember it?
That's why I don't often
I don't often film here.
Well...
It's funny.
Yes, you see...
I was filming
The product introduction video.
I didn't start filming until halfway through.
Yes, sir.
So, in the end...
I'll shoot it at home.
Um, I'm sorry, it's very...
I thought I got it, but I didn't.
Sad thing happened.
I'm going to introduce the products now, even though I'm dead.
I'll try my best to get back on track.
Okay, so, when I was taking
When I was taking pictures of the products
I was taking product introductions for a long time, well, I mean, there was a long period of time.
I hadn't even used it once when I introduced it.
But now, today, it's in use.
I'm using it now.
And, there are new things that have been added.
I'm going to introduce them as well.
Here we go!
The first one is a white cup.
Clang, clang, clang, clang, clang!
What a surprise!
This is a white cup.
I bought these in Yamanashi, and I bought them at various camping stores.
250, 250 smaller.
This one, this one, this one, this one.
This is 500, this is 500.
I bought these cups.
I buy these cups every time I go to a store or something, and if I see something I think is cute, I buy it.
It's fun to collect them.
Then, this one.
What's this?
It's really popular.
I asked the guy at the store.
and he said that people come here for this.
But he said it's not the right time anymore.
Here it is!
Ta-da!
This is dirty.
Rini.
It's a pot from Lini Flame.
It's a fire pot.
I've used it so much.
I can't get it off.
I'm trying to get it dirty.
It's so cute.
I really wanted a small one, but they only had big ones.
But with the members...
I think it's good for when we do it with the members.
It's so cute.
It's like...
Pots and pans and everything.Pots, everything.
You can do anything.
Um...
Udon
Stewed udon
Oden
Shabu-shabu.
Tomato nabe
It's a nabe that can be used for anything.
It's a hot pot!
I wanted it in winter.
I wanted to get it in winter.
Next
Ta-da!
Cool stuff!
A batoning knife.
This is dangerous.
It's a batoning knife.
You have to be very careful with it.
A batoning knife.
With this...
Cut the rolls.
Cut the rolls into tiny pieces.
Feather sticks.
It's cool.
I think it's pretty cool.
Next up...
Look at that!
Oh!
Firestarter!
I bought this at a hundred-yen store.
I'll put it on at 100 yen.
I'll put it on.
It's dangerous.
I can't do it.
Just swipe it on.
Put it on the twine.
I don't know...
Before introducing our products...
Before introducing the products...
Takebi.
I took it when it was my second time.
I didn't use this at all.
I didn't use this kind of equipment at all and I didn't have all the tools at all.
I've started to use them for camping videos now.
And this.
I think it's from Celia. I bought this at Celia. I'm going to buy coffee at a convenience store.
This is it.
I already have it after I use it.
It's not so pretty.
And this.
And this is what you need with it.
HILKY BOW
Shaqing.
Isn't it cool?
Oh, I'm gonna lip it.
Shaqeen.
It's so cute!
It's so good!
This is not cheap, but it's not cheap at all, it's like a 100-yen store or something.
It's a skibo, but it's a little bit...
It's super cute!
It's really good! It's super cute!
It's so cute!
I think I'll go with this one.
Isn't it cute?
There's one that looks like a ladle spoon.
And this one that doesn't hold the ladle.
I bought one that only takes the juice from the ingredients.
Cute! Gray!
It's cute!
Cute!
I like the color.
I like the material.
I was going to go with stainless steel.
but I thought it would be better to use a lighter one.I knew the lighter the better.
So, here it is.
I can't really use soup, but...
but I thought I could use something else.
You know...
Meat
Stir-fried meat...
I thought maybe I could use something like that.
So I decided on this one.
I thought it could be used in various ways.
This...
This is for seasonings. It's from a hundred-yen store.
It's in there right now, but it can hold seasonings like this.
It can hold powder and liquid.
I haven't used this one yet, but I want to.
And I also bought a spoon and fork. I've been using disposable ones because they're a pain to wash.
I bought a spoon and fork at Smoke Eat because I wanted to look cool!
It's so cute!
It's not easy to store it.
It's so light! It's so light!
It looks so easy to eat! Looks so easy to eat!
I haven't even used this one yet!
It's so cute!
The butt!
Can't wait to use it!
And now for the spices!
Ta-da!
Holenessi and Jaco!
Holenessi is a classic of all classics.
We have some of this at home.
We use it in our cooking.
It's so good!
You can put it on meat, you can put it on stir-fried vegetables.
You can use it on anything.
I use it for net sambo.
It's also great!
You can use it on anything if you have one.
It's really good.
I just started living alone.
I need a lot of spices.
If you don't have enough, this one will do the trick.
It's really good!
I recommend this meat.
Do you know anything about it?
Many people know.
This is called Yakou... where was it?
Somewhere... Somewhere...
When we went to Camp Gia's.
I went to a Camp Gia store... and I had a sample.
I was able to eat it, along with the food.
And it was kind of...
Is it dry?
No, I don't know what dry is.
It's totally fine. I can eat it.
It's kind of hot.
I don't know.
It's not spicy.
It's really good.
I wanted a different spice for my eyes.
I got it.
I use these two basically. I also use salt, and I have soy sauce and olive oil.
Yes, I think it's like this. I'm going to cut the product introduction.
Yes, that's what I'm talking about.
I'm so sorry for the emergency.
I didn't expect this house to appear so soon.
I'm glad we were able to get it.
So...
I'm glad I was able to get a good look at the house.
Bye bye!
See you next week!
Good button too!